好吧  乔伊  你能办到的
All right, Joey. You got this.
在这个弱不禁风的身体里面
Inside this scrawny, un-athletic, muscle-free sack of bones
是一个往返跑高手
is a natural-born shuttle runner.
您这么对我说我很荣幸
That means a lot coming from you.
但是丝毫无用啊
But it's useless.
我不可能在 35 秒里面跑完往返跑
There is no way I can do this in 35 seconds.
我的结业致辞就算是泡汤了
I can kiss valedictorian a good-bye.
老兄  你能行的
Dude, it's going to be okay.
你只要充分信任你的第一感觉
Just trust your instincts.
这个叫迪吉的兄弟多少还是有些锦囊妙计的
And know that the dig-man still has a couple tricks up his sleeve.
还有  你最好把鞋带系好
Also, you might want to tie your shoe.
啊  呵呵  是啊
Ah, pfft. Yeah.
准备好了么  乔伊
All right, Joey.
这是你往返跑补考的唯一一次机会
You get one last shot to pass your shuttle run.
好的
Okay.
在此之前  我有个问题
But before we do this... question.
- 跑  - 好的
- Go! - Okay.
不要
No!
恶心
Gross!
快跑啊  乔伊  快跑
Run, Joey, run!
乔伊  你想和我一起去舞会吗
Joey, you want to go to prom?
不  不  不  不  不
No no no no no!
25.4 秒  你打破了校记录
25.4. That's a new school record.
我的儿子是个运动员
My son's a jock.
我的儿子居然是个运动员
My son's a jock!
好啊
Yeah.
多谢了  迪吉  这事没了你成不了
Thanks, Diggie. Couldn't have done it without you.
恭喜啦  亲爱的
Congratulations, little man.
谢谢了
Thanks.
我已经累得跑不动了
I'm too tired to run away.
我知道
I know.